THE CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS AND EVENTS OF THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL.
本剧中的人物、地点、组织 和事件均为虚构。
You must be very busy, Mr. Jung.
郑先生，您一定很忙。
I came here by boat
我坐船来到这里
and I don't even know if I'll be able to see it.
我什至不知道我是否能看到它。
I'll go straight to see her.
我这就去见她。
See you at the bar.
酒吧见。
My man is in the hall,
我的男人在大厅里
ask him what you need.
问他你需要什么。
Well goodbye.
那再见吧;好吧再见。
Sorry.
对不起。
Isn't this place very elegant?
这个地方是不是很优雅？
Good food will give you energy.
好的食物会给你能量。
I'm sure your mother wants you to feel well soon.
我相信你妈妈希望 你尽快好起来。
Do not talk about it.
不要谈论它。
Euijeong.
义正.
When we were kids,
当我们还是孩子的时候，
I fled without saying anything.
我二话没说就逃走了。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
Why did you do that?
你为什么这么做？
I didn't want to cause you problems.
我不想给你带来麻烦。
The entire neighborhood would have denounced us as murderers.
整个邻居都会 谴责我们是杀人犯。
Do you remember the dream we were talking about?
你还记得我们谈论过的梦想吗？
More or less.
或多或少。
It almost came true, didn't it?
这几乎成真了，不是吗？
How many locations do you have?
你们有多少个地点？
Most are run by my employees.
大多数都是由我的员工管理的。
All together...
全部一起...
I have many.
我有很多。
How did you manage to open so many stores?
你是怎么开这么多店的？
It seems like you work with your old friends.
看起来你就像和你的老朋友一起工作。
Are they your partners?
他们是你的伙伴吗？
Or your employees?
或者你的员工？
You make a lot of questions.
你提出了很多问题。
I want to know what happened to your life.
我想知道你的生活发生了什么。
I also want to know about you.
我也想了解你。
So, you fulfilled your dream.
所以，你实现了你的梦想。
Now I should keep my promise.
现在我应该遵守我的诺言。
What promise?
什么承诺？
What is your dream?
你的梦想是什么？
My dream?
我的梦想？
Have a nightclub?
有夜总会吗？
It's the most specific dream I ever heard.
这是我听过的最具体的梦。
Not just a nightclub.
不仅仅是一家夜总会。
I want to open a restaurant and cafe next to the nightclub.
我想 在夜总会旁边开一家餐厅和咖啡馆。
And a cinema, a Chinese restaurant, a bar and a Korean restaurant.
还有电影院、中餐厅、 酒吧和韩国餐厅。
So, whoever visits Gangnam, will come to all my stores.
所以，无论谁来江南， 都会来我所有的商店。
And everyone will respect me.
每个人都会尊重我。
You would be like a "tycoon of the night."
你会像一个“夜间大亨”。
A tycoon?
大亨？
I like it.
我喜欢。
If I become this famous,
如果我变得这么出名的话
I won't have to go to expensive universities to marry you.
我不必去昂贵的大学 来嫁给你。
What are you saying?
你在说什么？
I will become a tycoon.
我会成为大亨。
I will become a tycoon and marry you.
我会成为大亨并嫁给你。
I promise.
我保证。
THE WORST OF EVIL
最邪恶的事
Where are the Chinese?
中国人在哪里？
Now they are up.
现在他们起来了。
Any problem?
任何问题？
No, boss.
不，老板。
Where was it?
它在哪里？
Hello, this is Jung Gicheul.
大家好，我是郑基哲。
I arrived.
我到了。
Thank you for coming here.
谢谢你来到这里。
You can use it during your stay.
您可以在住宿期间使用它。
Are you fucking with me?
你在玩弄我吗？
What is this?
这是什么？
A gift for you.
一个给你的礼物。
Professor Yoon used the same one.
尹教授用的是同一个。
Is that how you handle everything?
你就是这样处理一切的吗？
Man...
男人...
You don't even have a fucking lighter?
你他妈的连打火机都没有吗？
Oye.
奥耶。
With the losses we suffer
伴随着我们遭受的损失
in getting the boat and crew ready...
准备好船 和船员......
Don't you owe me at least a gold watch?
你不至少欠我一块金表吗？
I apologize again.
我再次表示歉意。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
It will not happen again.
不会有下一次。
I only work with people I can trust.
我只 与我可以信任的人一起工作。
That's what my father always says.
这是我父亲常说的。
So that we can trade again as before,
这样我们就可以像以前一样进行交易，
We will regain confidence.
我们将重拾信心。
Restore confidence?
恢复信心？
As they say here,
正如他们在这里所说的，
keep dreaming, Mr. Jung.
继续梦想吧，荣格先生。
What else can I do for you?
我还能为您做什么？
The Japanese must have many contacts.
日本人 一定有很多接触。
I don't know how they did it, but they called my father
我不知道他们是怎么做到的， 但他们给我父亲打电话
to suggest that the three of us meet in Korea.
建议 我们三人在韩国见面。
That's why I'm here.
这就是我在这里的原因。
But why meet in person if we can talk on the phone?
但如果我们可以通过电话交谈，为什么还要亲自见面呢？
I think I know why.
我想我知道为什么。
I'm tired. Leave.
我累了。离开。
Haeryun.
海云。
We want to increase imports
我们要增加进口
8 to 10 kilos.
8至10公斤。
We will pay the extra charge, not Japan.
我们将支付 额外费用，而不是日本。
He became very generous when he learned that the Japanese were coming,
当他得知日本人要来时，他变得非常慷慨，
Mr. Jung.
郑先生。
Too late.
为时已晚。
-This is Oyama. -Hello.
——这是小山。 -你好。
See you tomorrow at 2:00 pm
明天下午 2:00 见
Are you in Korea?
你在韩国吗？
Did father come too?
爸爸也来了吗？
Tomorrow I will inform you of the location.
明天我会告诉你地点。
Mr. Murayama from Japan called.
日本村山先生打来电话。
He said that the bosses of the Yokohama branch of the Yoshioka-gumi
他说，吉冈组横滨支部的老板们
They are heading to Korea.
他们正前往韩国。
Se llama Oyama Tsuyoshi.
Se llama 小山刚。
You will also stay at the Grand Plaza Hotel in Gangnam,
您还将入住 江南大广场酒店，
just like the Chinese.
就像中国人一样。
You will occupy room 608.
您将入住608房间。
And the Chinese?
那么中国人呢？
In rooms 850 and 851.
在 850 和 851 房间。
Maybe they will come to talk about the attack
也许他们会来谈论这次袭击
who interrupted the purchase.
谁中断了购买。
It would be nice to put microphones in the rooms.
如果房间里能安装麦克风就好了。
Then we asked for the court order.
然后我们要求法庭命令。
Inspectors will monitor cameras in the hotel hallways.
检查员将监控 酒店走廊的摄像头。
When we see them enter the same room or go somewhere,
当我们看到他们进入 同一个房间或去某个地方时，
we will plant microphones in every room.
我们将在每个房间安装麦克风。
If Jung Gicheul meets them,
如果郑基哲遇见他们，
It would be ideal if Inspector Park was also there.
如果朴督察也在的话就更完美了。
If so...
如果是这样...
Toma.
托马。
This microphone covers a radius of one kilometer.
该麦克风的覆盖 半径为一公里。
Inspector Park will carry this.
朴督察将携带这个。
I will listen to everything that happens
我会倾听发生的一切
and I will record in real time.
我会实时记录。
Finished?
完成的？
I'm leaving then.
那我就走了。
The triangle of three countries.
三个国家的三角。
The international poster.
国际海报。
By the way, Mr. Cho,
顺便说一下，曹先生，
When can Inspector Yoo stop seeing Jung Gicheul?
刘警官什么时候才能 不再见到郑基哲呢？
We don't want to do this either.
我们也不想这样做。
We can't let it disappear suddenly.
我们不能让它 突然消失。
Let's arrest them all with the evidence we get now
让我们 用现在掌握的证据将他们全部逮捕
and let's close the case quickly.
让我们尽快结案吧。
GANGNAM POLICE STATION
江南警察局
What is the name of the missing person?
失踪者的名字是什么？
Cho Janghyun.
曹长贤.
But they call him Manager Cho.
但他们叫他曹经理。
Manager of what company?
什么公司的经理？
Which was?
哪一个是？
Of our company.
我们公司的。
When did you lose contact with him?
你什么时候和他失去联系的？
-Well... -Jeez...
-嗯...- 天啊...
That's not what happened.
事实并非如此。
Was it last Monday?
是上周一吗？
I do not know.
我不知道。
Last Monday
上周一
They kidnapped him before our eyes.
他们在我们眼前绑架了他。
This is very frustrating.
这非常令人沮丧。
He was kidnapped?
他被绑架了？
Cho, the drug addict?
Cho，吸毒者？
-Yeah.
-是的。
-Roll up your sleeves. -That?
-卷起你的袖子。 -那？
Let's go. Arremánguense.
我们走吧。阿雷姆??nguense。
Why is your arm so dirty?
你的手臂怎么这么脏？
They are Manager Cho's henchmen.
他们是曹经理的心腹。
Sorry?
对不起？
So, to Manager Cho
那么，对于曹经理来说
he was kidnapped?
他被绑架了？
There is something called Gangnam Crystal.
有一种东西叫江南水晶。
It is a popular type of methamphetamine.
它是一种流行的甲基苯丙胺。
Who's your boss?
你的老板是谁？
There is a drug dealer called Yankees,
有一个毒贩叫Yankees，
We told him to bring his boss.
我们告诉他带他的老板来。
We brought that guy in, and three took Manager Cho.
我们带了那个人进来， 三个人带了赵经理。
We have to catch that Yankees guy,
我们必须抓住那个洋基队的家伙
but we don't know where to start
但我们不知道从哪里开始
-and we don't have... -Hey!
-我们没有... -嘿！
Are you high? Why do you ramble?
你高吗？你为什么要闲逛？
Tell me about that Yankees guy.
跟我说说那个洋基队的家伙吧。
And stop crying.
别哭了。
We took him in, beat him up and asked him questions.
我们把他带进来，殴打他 并问他问题。
-To Yankees? -Yeah.
-去洋基队？ -是的。
-AND? -All the names he said
-和？ -他说的所有名字
They were fake.
它们是假的。
But we noticed that they are all from Yeoksam High School.
但我们注意到 他们都是驿三高中的学生。
Yeoksam High School.
驿三高中。
As?
作为？
Dime.
十分钱。
How did they know?
他们怎么知道的？
I checked his pockets.
我检查了他的口袋。
An entrance to Dongdaemun Baseball Stadium.
东大门棒球场的入口。
¿Y?
??是？
That day, there was a game
那天，有一场比赛
entre Yeoksam
驿三间
the Gwangju Jail.
光州监狱。
-The game that day? -Yeah.
-那天的比赛？ -是的。
¿Yeoksam versus Gwangju Jeil?
??驿三VS光州监狱？
-Yeah!
-是的！
-That's why Yeoksam High School. -Yeah.
-这就是驿三高中的原因。 -是的。
How retarded.
多么迟钝啊。
We solved it.
我们解决了。
Yeoksam High School graduates are very close-knit
驿三高中毕业生 关系非常密切
-in Gangnam. -Yeah.
-在江南。 -是的。
Clear.
清除。
¿Hola?
？？你好？
Come to the Grand Plaza Hotel.
来到广场大酒店。
Bring the Chinese.
把中国人带过来。
Good. I will go with them.
好的。我会和他们一起去。
Then I'll tell you where in the hotel.
然后我会告诉你酒店的位置。
Can I go with my men?
我可以和我的男人一起去吗？
Bring only one bodyguard.
只带一名保镖。
Kwon Seungho.
权胜浩.
Yes Boss?
是的，老板？
accompany me
陪伴我
The rest wait at the hotel door.
其余人在酒店门口等候。
With discretion.
酌情决定。
What the fuck?
搞什么鬼？
Hey, cum!
嘿，暨！
Fool.
傻子。
Where are you going in such a hurry?
这么着急你要去哪里？
You almost ran him over.
你差点把他撞倒了。
-Excuse me, sir. -You almost ran him over.
-对不起，先生。 -你差点把他撞倒了。
You believe yourself more for having a Mercedes.
你因为拥有一辆奔驰而更加相信自己。
Get out of the car.
从车里出去。
-Damn... -Come on.
-该死... - 来吧。
Low. I am Police.
低的。我是警察。
What an idiot.
真是个傻瓜。
Drive better, bad boy.
开得更好，坏孩子。
Hello, Mr. Jung. So long.
你好，郑先生。这么久。
Wait.
等待。
Oh, the back.
哦，背面。
Low. I want to talk to you.
低的。我想跟你说话。
What the fuck?
搞什么鬼？
Listen.
听。
What are you doing now?
你在干什么？
Do you have an order?
您有订单吗？
Where did you get that from the order?
你从哪里得到的订单？
I asked if you have a fucking order.
我问你他妈有没有订单。
You're a...
你是一个...
I've never seen this face.
我从来没有见过这张脸。
You are new?
你是新来的吗？
Bad fucking birth.
他妈的出生不好。
Isn't it going to go down?
不是要跌了吗？
Curse.
诅咒。
-What's happening? -Mr. Jung.
-发生了什么？ -先生。荣格.
You know Yankees, right?
你知道洋基队，对吧？
Looks like he got rid of a drug addict named Manager Cho.
看来他摆脱了 一个名叫曹经理的吸毒者。
I wanted to talk to him, but I can't reach him.
我想和他说话， 但我联系不上他。
It's one of yours. He should know where she is.
这是你的之一。他应该知道她在哪里。
Where is?
哪里？
Do not know him.
不认识他。
Listen.
听。
Are you serious?
你是认真的？
They are both in Gangnam night.
他们都在江南之夜。
And they all went to Yeoksam High School.
他们都去 了驿三高中。
Hola, inspector.
你好，督察。
What brings you here?
什么风把你吹到这儿？
Are you okay, inspector?
你还好吗，督察？
Hello, Jungbae.
你好，正培。
No, because of you, idiots.
不，因为你们，白痴。
Jungbae, Heesung.
正裴、熙成。
-Yeah. -Do you know Yankees?
-是的。 -你知道洋基队吗？
That? Yankees?
那？洋基队？
I don't know who it is.
我不知道是谁。
Come on. They must know it. He went to his school.
快点。他们一定知道这一点。 他去了他的学校。
I went to Yeoksam High School, the worst school ever.
我去了驿三高中， 这是有史以来最差的学校。
I know that you take care of the alumni.
我知道你很照顾校友。
Come on, inspector.
来吧，督察。
In our school, there are 12 courses for each year.
我们学校 每年有12门课程。
And more than 50 students in each one. We don't know them all
每所都有50多名学生。 我们并不认识他们所有人
I can question them to see if it's true.
我可以质问他们，看看这是否属实。
Inspector.
督察。
Excuse me, but we're busy.
对不起，我们很忙。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
Hey, Jung Gicheul.
嘿，郑基哲。
If his henchman Yankees killed Manager Cho,
如果他的心腹洋基队 杀了赵经理
It will not be a drug crime.
这不会是毒品犯罪。
It will be a violent crime.
这将是一种暴力犯罪。
What do you think it means?
你认为这意味着什么？
That you will see me often.
你会经常见到我。
See you.
再见。
Here is your key.
这是你的钥匙。
What is your name?
你叫什么名字？
¿Yankees?
??洋基队？
Viejo...
别霍...
We'll see each other more often.
我们会更频繁地见面。
That? He said he was busy.
那？他说他很忙。
Keep going.
继续前进。
You don't have to accompany me.
你不必陪我。
They won't go straight to that Yankees guy
他们不会直接去找那个洋基队的家伙
just because he named it
只因为他给它起的名字
Why do we follow them?
我们为什么要跟随他们？
We have nothing to do.
我们无事可做。
Are you busy?
你忙吗？
Let's follow them for today
今天就让我们跟随他们
Let's see where they come together
让我们看看他们在哪里聚集在一起
and what are they doing these days.
他们这些天在做什么。
I think we lost them.
我想我们失去了他们。
Alright. It's a fucking Mercedes.
好吧。这是一辆他妈的奔驰。
A Mercedes can be seen from 100 meters.
100米外就能看到一辆奔驰。
-Hello. -Come to room 1203.
-你好。 -来到1203房间。
The security office is clear, over.
保卫处 清空，结束。
Good. All areas are clear.
好的。所有区域都清晰可见。
There are no signs of intruders.
没有入侵者的迹象。
The parking lot is clear.
停车场很干净。
Park Junmo. Good.
朴俊模. 好的。
Jung Gicheul arrived at the hotel. Pay attention.
郑基哲抵达酒店。 注意。
Proceed only when we have the evidence.
只有当我们有证据时才继续进行。
The microphone covers a radius of one kilometer.
麦克风覆盖 半径一公里。
Inspector Park will carry this.
朴督察将携带这个。
I will listen to everything that happens
我会倾听发生的一切
and I will record in real time.
我会实时记录。
They are taking the elevator.
他们正在乘电梯。
The Koreans entered the lobby.
韩国人进入大厅。
They'll be up to one soon.
他们很快就会达到一个目标。
What floor is it on?
它在几楼？
On the 12th floor.
在12楼。
It's Hwang Mingoo, the policeman.
我是警察黄民高。
There's someone in the hallway.
走廊里有人。
The Koreans reached the 12th floor.
韩国人到达了12楼。
Before entering, curl them.
进入之前，将它们卷曲。
¿Cachearlos?
??卡查洛斯？
One of the Koreans passed by.
一名韩国人路过。
It's the second's turn.
轮到第二个了。
It just can't be.
这是不可能的。
Are you fucking with me?
你在玩弄我吗？
You are very meticulous.
你很细心。
-Activate the fire alarm. -That?
- 启动火警警报器。 -那？
Activate the fire alarm right now!
立即启动火警警报！
Stop touching me. Perhaps you like?
别再碰我了。也许你喜欢？
Come on. The fire alarm!
快点。火警警报！
I'll go see what's going on.
我去看看发生了什么事。
Dohyung.
道亨。
The Japanese are frisking us.
日本人正在搜身我们。
I'll have to throw away the microphone.
我得把麦克风扔掉。
I'm going to throw it away.
我要把它扔掉。
Wait.
等待。
I think I can handle it.
我想我能应付。
It was a false alarm.
这是一场虚惊。
Take them to the room and wait.
带他们去房间等待。
Curse.
诅咒。
Down the volume. It's very high.
降低音量。这是非常高的。
Motherfucker.
混蛋。
Hey, can't you talk?
嘿，你不能说话吗？
You must be very shy.
你一定很害羞。
The Japanese police began to monitor us.
日本警察开始监视我们。
Father couldn't come?
父亲不能来吗？
If possible,
如果可能的话，
I would like to meet his father in China.
我想在中国见见他的父亲。
You can meet me.
你可以来见见我。
Aren't you the boss in Japan?
你不是日本的老板吗？
How is Professor Yoon?
尹教授怎么样了？
Splendid. We treat her very well.
灿烂。我们对她很好。
Do you know her well?
你很了解她吗？
We bought a lot of product from them 20 years ago.
20年前我们从他们那里购买了很多产品。
What's that?
那是什么？
It's the advance they gave me.
这是他们给我的预付款。
Why do you return it?
为什么要退货？
Are you going out of business?
你要倒闭吗？
No.
不。
We will resend the product, and when it arrives well,
我们将重新发送产品， 当产品顺利到达时，
They will pay us.
他们会付钱给我们。
Then you will get paid later.
然后你稍后就会得到报酬。
Isn't that a lot of formality?
这不是很正式吗？
And the traitor?
那么叛徒呢？
They found him?
他们找到他了？
Yeah.
是的。
Who was?
谁是？
One of our members.
我们的成员之一。
Did you have direct involvement in this?
您直接参与了这件事吗？
No.
不。
Do you know about our business?
您了解我们的业务吗？
Like I just said,
就像我刚才说的，
the police are watching us.
警察正在监视我们。
Could it be because of Song Donghyuk?
难道是因为宋东赫？
He must have told his gang
他一定告诉了他的帮派
that he was going to meet father.
他要去见父亲。
But he never came back, maybe they reported him missing,
但他再也没有回来， 也许他们报告说他失踪了，
and the Japanese police found out.
日本警方发现了这一点。
So, it's not for you, but for us?
那么，这不是为了你， 而是为了我们？
It's possible that you too
有可能你也是
be watched because of the traitor.
因为叛徒而被监视。
The bag you brought.
你带来的包。
Put it down, stand there for five minutes and come back
放下它，站在那里五分钟，然后回来
as if you were waiting for the drug dealer.
就像你在等待毒贩一样。
So I can see from here
所以我可以从这里看到
if the police follow you.
如果警察跟踪你。
And whether you're with a drug dealer or not.
以及无论你是否与毒贩在一起。
Is it a father's order?
这是父亲的命令吗？
You do not want to do it?
你不想做吗？
Then, the deal is over.
然后，交易就结束了。
Is it the end of our business?
我们的生意就此结束了吗？
What a pity.
真可惜。
Those morons are planning to get us.
那些白痴正计划抓捕我们。
We still waiting?
我们还在等吗？
That?
那？
They wait too.
他们也在等待。
Hwang Mingoo, how damn.
黄珉豪，真是该死。
Why does he always screw us?
为什么他总是欺负我们？
What's happening?
发生了什么？
I think it just came out.
我想它刚刚出来。
In fact, I made it go down
事实上，我让它下降了
so we could talk alone.
这样我们就可以单独交谈。
You want to deal directly with us, right?
您想直接与我们打交道 ，对吗？
Because without intermediaries,
因为没有中介，
We can divide the money that goes to Mr. Jung.
我们可以分给郑先生的钱。
Maybe something went wrong.
也许出了什么问题。
I'm with the woman from China.
我和那个来自中国的女人在一起。
I'll let them talk.
我会让他们说话。
Damn.
该死。
Those idiots always complicate everything.
那些白痴总是让一切变得复杂。
Captain, are you waiting for a drug dealer?
队长，你在等 毒贩吗？
Should we arrest him when he sees someone?
当他看到某人时我们应该逮捕他吗？
Do not move. Let's wait for now.
不要动。我们现在就等等吧。
They wait...
他们等...
What do you think is in the bag that criminal is carrying?
你认为 罪犯携带的包里有什么？
Something stolen?
东西被偷了？
Drugs?
毒品？
Can I call you Miss Lee?
我可以叫你李小姐吗？
Soy Kim Hwaseong.
大豆金华城.
He must be Mr. Jung's father.
他一定是荣格先生的父亲。
My last name is Kim.
我姓金。
He asked me if we wanted to deal directly without Jung Gicheul.
他问我是否想 在没有郑基哲的情况下直接进行交易。
Do you know why I used Gicheul as a carrier
你知道我为什么用Gicheul 作为载体吗
and I made him rich?
我让他变得富有？
I'm about to become
我即将成为
in the Yoshioka-gumi boss.
在吉冈组老板那里。
I don't want to get involved in drug trafficking.
我不想参与 贩毒活动。
Curse.
诅咒。
We are about to witness an exchange.
我们即将见证一场交流。
That means I need to be invisible in this business.
这意味着我需要 在这个行业中保持隐形。
So that, even if the Japanese police investigate me,
所以 即使日本警方调查我
It seems like everything was the work of a Korean band
看起来一切都是 韩国乐队的作品
that sells illegally imported merchandise from China in Japan.
该公司在日本销售 从中国非法进口的商品。
That's why.
这就是为什么。
The Korean band will be solely responsible.
韩国乐队 将全权负责。
What do you want to do now?
你现在想做什么？
What a bummer.
真是太糟糕了。
We can replace Gicheul.
我们可以取代吉彻尔。
I have many friends in Korea.
我在韩国有很多朋友。
We can choose one of them.
我们可以选择其中之一。
My question is
我的问题是
If you could produce a product of the same quality
如果你能生产出 同等质量的产品
and send it in perfect condition, just as you have been doing.
并将其完好无损地发送出去， 就像您一直在做的那样。
Do you think you could do that?
你认为你能做到吗？
I decide that.
我决定了。
I decide which Korean
我决定哪个韩国人
I want to sell you our product.
我想向您推销我们的产品。
From what Gicheul pays him,
从吉切尔付给他的钱中，
I will pay you 15% more.
我将多付给你 15%。
We came to look for Yankees,
我们来寻找洋基队，
and we have a bigger one.
我们有一个更大的。
Who are these cretins?
这些白痴是谁？
Damn.
该死。
Where did they go?
他们去哪儿了？
They are very fast.
他们非常快。
Detenlos.
德特洛斯。
-Stop there. -Inspector.
-停在那里。 -检查员。
We have something to do here.
我们在这里有事要做。
I said stop.
我说停下来。
Everything is alright now?
现在一切都好吗？
That's for Miss Lee to decide.
这是由李小姐决定的。
Hey, Chinese.
嘿，中国人。
Don't you speak Korean?
你不会说韩语吗？
You do not speak
你别说
Korean?
韩国人？
Your boss speaks fluent Korean.
你的老板会说一口流利的韩语。
Do you understand me or not?
你到底懂不懂我？
Why is there so much silence?
为什么如此沉默？
Do you still use matches?
你还在用火柴吗？
Are you from the Qing dynasty or what?
你是清朝人还是什么？
Take. Keep him.
拿。留下他。
I give it to you. Take it.
我把它给你。拿去。
The police came.
警察来了。
A policeman comes.
一名警察来了。
I take care of everything there.
我照顾那里的一切。
You flee with those inside...
你和里面的人一起逃走...
¡Oye!
??哎呀！
I said the police came. Understood?
我说警察来了。明白了吗？
Take them and run. Now.
带上他们就跑。现在。
Inspector.
督察。
What brings you here?
什么风把你吹到这儿？
What do you think?
你怎么认为？
I told you you'd see me again.
我告诉过你你会再见到我的。
What is Jung Gicheul doing there?
郑基哲在那里做什么？
He is doing business.
他正在做生意。
Business, of course? Cum.
当然是做生意吗？暨。
I said cum.
我说暨。
You heard me?
你听到了吗？
Stop looking at me and cum.
别再看着我了。
-Hey. -I'm sorry.
-嘿。 -对不起。
Did you go crazy? Cum.
你疯了吗？暨。
¡Oiga, Sr. Jung!
??老奥伊加。荣格！
¡Young Gicheul!
??年轻的基切尔！
There is.
有。
¡Oiga, Sr. Jung!
??老奥伊加。荣格！
Jung Gicheul, come here.
郑基哲，你过来。
Mr. Jung. Listen!
郑先生。听！
-Let's finish our conversation. -What were they doing?
-让我们结束我们的谈话吧。 -他们在干什么？
Did they play poker?
他们玩扑克吗？
Come here.
过来。
¡Alto!
??阿尔托！
Stop there, you bastard!
站住吧，你这个混蛋！
Did you go crazy?
你疯了吗？
Come on, inspector.
来吧，督察。
-Do not be like that. -You hit me?
-不要那样。 -你打我？
Are you spotting me?
你发现我了吗？
Come here, you bad boy.
过来，你这个坏孩子。
Mr. Jung, does that mean our deal is off?
郑先生， 这是否意味着我们的交易取消了？
I think so.
我想是这样。
It seems like she trusts her man a lot.
看来她非常信任自己的男人。
Go help Mr. Jung's man.
去帮助郑先生的人吧。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
Inspectors, go to the 12th floor.
检查员，去12楼。
-Where are they? -Here.
-他们在哪里？ -这里。
-We found them. -Arrest him.
-我们找到了他们。 -逮捕他。
To which of the two?
两者中的哪一个？
Who the hell are you?
你到底是谁？
-To the big guy. -Good.
-给大佬。 -好的。
-Want to die? -Fuck off.
-想死吗？ -滚开。
Motherfucker.
混蛋。
-High! -What do they do?
-高的！ -他们在做什么？
Who are you?
你是谁？
He is arrested.
他被捕了。
-Let go of me, you bastards. -Stop moving.
-放开我，你们这些混蛋。 -停止移动。
I'm a policeman, you idiots!
我是警察，你们这些白痴！
I'm a real cop, for God's sake!
看在上帝的份上，我是一名真正的警察！
Sons of bitches!
狗娘养的！
The fucking mother!
该死的妈妈！
Captain, you really are a police officer.
队长，你真是一名警察。
Police?
警察？
And the other guy?
另一个人呢？
He escaped.
他逃走了。
Back off right now.
立即退后。
The fucking mother. Idiots!
该死的妈妈。白痴！
Are you OK?
你还好吗？
Yes I'm fine.
是的，我没事。
Let's go out when everything calms down.
等一切平静下来我们就出去吧。
Yes Boss.
是的，老板。
Fucking police!
他妈的警察！
You should have bribed him.
你应该贿赂他。
Damn.
该死。
We could let the policeman in.
我们可以让警察进来。
Chatting is not illegal.
聊天并不违法。
That policeman would have found something for us.
那个警察会为我们找到一些东西的。
And your passport
还有你的护照
Isn't it fake?
不是假的吗？
were you protecting me
你是在保护我吗
of an arrest?
逮捕？
It sounds like you had an intense fight.
听起来你们经历了一场激烈的战斗。
Does it mean everything will get worse?
这是否意味着一切都会变得更糟？
Making everything worse must be a quality of yours.
让一切变得更糟一定是你的品质。
Mr. Jung, you have a very wild way of doing business.
郑先生，您 做生意的方式非常疯狂。
It is very dangerous to work with you.
和你一起工作是非常危险的。
I got this injury recently.
我最近受了这个伤。
It's not serious.
这并不严重。
And until now,
而直到现在，
We never had problems caused by issues like that.
我们从未遇到过 由此类问题引起的问题。
I assure you.
我向你们保证。
I understand.
我明白。
For you, it's not even a problem.
对你来说，这甚至都不是问题。
Could you at least do something about the wound on your back?
你至少能 对你背上的伤口做点什么吗？
Someone could report you for murder.
有人可能会举报你 谋杀。
Come here.
过来。
Heal the wound.
治愈伤口。
He risked his life to take responsibility,
他冒着生命危险去承担责任，
which is a good quality in a business partner.
这是商业伙伴的良好品质。
That heavy!
好重啊！
How many times do I have to repeat it?
我需要重复多少次？
From room 1203
来自1203室
a group of people came out.
一群人走了出来。
Men and women.
男女。
And the room was huge!
而且房间很大！
It doesn't make sense that no one has booked it!
没有人预订就没有意义了！
No one booked room 1203 today.
今天没有人预订1203房间。
And who were those people?
那些人是谁？
Were they ghosts?
他们是鬼吗？
Tell me the truth, ma'am.
告诉我实话，女士。
Or you will have a criminal record.
否则你就会有犯罪记录。
Show me the book.
给我看看这本书。
Do you think I'm not serious?
你觉得我不认真吗？
Señor.
塞??或。
-I looked for them. -AND?
-我找过他们。 -和？
I can't find anyone.
我找不到人。
Damn.
该死。
Let's go then.
那我们走吧。
The Japanese suggested that we change Korean carrier.
日本人建议 我们换韩国航空公司。
And they will pay me 15% more than you pay me.
他们付给我的钱 比你付给我的多 15%。
We will pay you double
我们将付给你双倍工资
of what we paid per kilo.
我们每公斤支付的费用。
Money is not the problem here.
钱不是这里的问题。
What will you do to regain my trust?
你会做什么来重新获得我的信任？
It will be a difficult decision for us to start over with another one.
对我们来说，重新开始另一个决定将是一个艰难的决定。
What do we do?
我们做什么？
You have a good man willing to sacrifice himself
你有一个 愿意牺牲自己的好男人
for you.
为你。
I know that the Korean government is also very powerful.
我知道韩国政府 也很强大。
Now that the police got involved,
现在警察介入了，
Let's see how everything turns out.
让我们看看结果如何。
Why are you trying so hard?
你为什么这么努力？
Because I trust my boss.
因为我信任我的老板。
You value trust too, don't you?
你也很重视信任，不是吗？
We are equal. Trust is our priority.
我们是平等的。 信任是我们的首要任务。
Especially in this deal.
尤其是在这笔交易中。
What do you think
你怎么认为
of this madman?
这个疯子的？
He seems loyal.
他看起来很忠诚。
He seems like a good guy.
他看起来是个好人。
Hola.
你好。
I want to speak to room 608.
我想和 608 房间通话。
-Hello. -This is Miss Lee.
-你好。 ——这是李小姐。
Hola.
你好。
Should I decide today?
我今天应该决定吗？
I'll take a few days to think.
我要花几天时间考虑一下。
It's been a while since I've been to Korea.
我已经有一段时间没来韩国了。
I want to go out for a walk.
我想出去散步。
And let's see properties.
让我们看看属性。
Maybe I should stop sneaking money into China.
也许我应该停止 向中国偷钱。
You are likely to invest here.
您可能会在这里投资。
I'll need a tour guide.
我需要一个导游。
I guess you can't, right?
我想你不能，对吧？
You hit a police officer, you shouldn't draw attention to yourself.
你打了警察， 你不应该引起别人的注意。
¿Hola?
？？你好？
Are you with Miss Lee?
你和李小姐在一起吗？
Yeah.
是的。
Sr. Lee.
先生。李.
How impatient.
多么不耐烦啊。
I didn't expect him to call so soon.
我没想到他这么快就打电话来了。
The boss gave me
老板给了我
a message.
一个消息。
He says he will accept the decision you make.
他说他会接受 你的决定。
But no matter what your decision,
但无论你的决定是什么，
wants to suspend this deal for now.
希望暂时暂停这笔交易。
And as for the police interruption during the meeting,
至于 警察在会议期间打扰，
he is furious.
他很愤怒。
The police didn't come for this.
警察来不是为了这个。
Whatever the reason,
不管是什么原因，
He came for you, didn't he?
他是来找​​你的，不是吗？
Only when everything is safe again
只有当一切再次安全时
We will resume the deal.
我们将恢复交易。
Miss Lee.
李小姐。
I hope you make a sensible decision.
我希望你做出明智的决定。
Damn!
该死！
Mr. Jung, can we talk?
郑先生，我们可以谈谈吗？
Without customers, there is no point in producing.
没有客户，生产就没有意义。
That will weigh on my decision.
这将影响我的决定。
What can I do to help her?
我能做些什么来帮助她？
Can not do nothing.
不能什么都不做。
His Japanese father thinks he is a king.
他的日本父亲认为他是国王。
Assault on a police officer and obstruction of justice.
袭击警察 和妨碍司法公正。
Will you have gray hair when you get out of prison?
出狱后你的头发会变白吗？
I will also see you with gray hair.
我还会看到白发的你。
If everything goes well,
如果一切顺利的话
I want you to be my tour guide.
我想让你当我的导游。
-Odd. -Curse.
-奇怪的。 -诅咒。
Who are you?
你是谁？
I can help?
我可以搭把手？
We are police.
我们是警察。
Jung Gicheul is back, right?
郑基哲回来了是吗？
¡Gicheul!
??吉切尔！
Come out while I ask you nicely.
等我好声问你的时候你就出来吧。
What the fuck?
搞什么鬼？
¡Señor!
??Se??或者！
What the fuck is happening?
到底发生了什么？
Can you come see the cameras?
你能过来看看摄像机吗？
If you are going to investigate, bring a warrant.
如果你要调查， 请携带搜查令。
Like I always say,
就像我常说的，
these subordinates never listen.
这些下属从来不听。
Sons of bitches.
狗娘养的。
Here they come.
他们来了。
-Did they close the door? -That?
-他们关门了吗？ -那？
-The door. -Close the door, idiots!
-门。 -关上门，白痴！
¿"Industria Gangnam"?
??“工业江南”？
Of course.
当然。
Open. Police.
打开。警察。
Police. Open!
警察。打开！
What do we do, sir?
先生，我们该怎么办？
We did not commit any crime.
我们没有犯任何罪。
-I'm sorry -Did we do it?
-对不起 -我们做到了吗？
Aside.
在旁边。
Bad births.
不良出生。
Hey!
嘿！
Aren't they going to open?
他们不打算开门吗？
I'll give you three seconds.
我给你三秒钟。
Three.
三。
Of the!
的！
Sons of bitches.
狗娘养的。
One! Open the door, idiots!
一！开门吧，白痴们！
The fucking mother.
该死的妈妈。
Bad fucking births!
他妈的出生不好！
Open!
打开！
Open up, motherfuckers!
开放吧，混蛋们！
Damn!
该死！
Damn.
该死。
Bad births!
难产！
The fucking mother!
该死的妈妈！
Fools.
傻瓜。
What do you think it does?
你认为它有什么作用？
He looks like a construction worker.
他看起来像一名建筑工人。
Being a police officer does not give you the right to act like that.
作为一名警察并不意味着你有权利这样做。
Shit.
拉屎。
A police officer can act like that, son of a bitch.
一个警察就可以做出这样的事，狗娘养的。
That...?
那...？
Enough, brutes.
够了，畜生们。
Back. Get in line.
后退。排队。
-Curse. -In line, I said! Move!
-诅咒。 -排队，我说！移动！
Where is Jung Gicheul?
郑基哲在哪里？
I said he's not here.
我说他不在。
So, call him.
所以，给他打电话。
We don't know where he went.
我们不知道他去了哪里。
Call him on his cell phone, idiot.
用他的手机给他打电话，白痴。
He didn't give us his phone number.
他没有给我们他的电话号码。
What the fuck?
搞什么鬼？
He
他
didn't give you
没有给你
his phone number?
他的电话号码？
So,
所以，
Do you deserve some slaps?
你值得被打几巴掌吗？
Fool!
傻子！
A few?
一些？
That you say?
你说的是？
Is that right, son of a bitch?
是这样吗，王八蛋？
Hey!
嘿！
I guess you don't know his phone number either.
我猜你也不 知道他的电话号码。
I will help you
我会帮你
to remember
记住
GOOD.
好的。
Understood.
明白了。
They destroyed the office and left.
他们毁掉了办公室并离开了。
-What do we do? -The fucking mother.
-我们做什么？ -该死的妈妈。
Why Hwang Mingoo, who is a fucking lunatic?
为什么黄民浩 这个疯子？
SEO Boss.
搜索引擎优化老板。
Call emergency contacts
拨打紧急联系人电话
and tell them to close the premises and not show their heads.
并告诉他们关闭场所 ，不要露头。
All the premises?
所有场地？
Do what I tell you, you bastard.
照我说的做，你这个混蛋。
I will surrender.
我会投降。
That?
那？
Someone needs to take responsibility and resolve this.
需要有人承担责任 并解决这个问题。
I caused this problem,
我造成了这个问题，
so I'll put an end to it anyway.
所以无论如何我都会结束它。
Understanding, Kwon Seungho.
理解，权胜浩。
Unfortunate.
不幸的。
Do you think I'll let you go to jail?
你觉得我会让你进监狱吗？
Boss.
老板。
I will put an end to this
我会结束这一切
so nothing bad happens to you or the company.
所以 你或公司不会发生任何不好的事情。
In return...
作为回报...
If I can make everything calm down,
如果我能让一切平静下来
I want you to do me a favor.
我想让你帮我一个忙。
Business with Japan and China.
与日本和中国的业务。
I want to participate.
我想参加。
I'll go finish this.
我去完成这件事。
Answer me now, you bad boy.
现在就回答我吧，你这个坏孩子。
Subtitles: Daniela Costa
字幕：丹妮拉·科斯塔